#######################################################################
#-----KBNHUD v5 - Drums Of Heaven Edition - CHANGELOG-----#############
#######################################################################

#####################################################################
#-----ADDED-----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Added a "knedit" mode, with health and ammo displays (and their hangers-on) 
moved to be more widely spaced out on the horizonal axis; this mimics 
the KN Edit HUD often used by 6s players. - b1_rc7

-Added a fully functional set of replacement files to fix the loadout 
menus for 4:3 aspect ratios - b1_rc7

-Added a streaming mode similar to FlawHUD, budhud, flarepunch, and sunsetHUD - b1_rc4

-Added a whole new menu UI, main menu, backpack, loadout, store, and everything in between. - b1_rc1, finished v5_final

-Added color customization back to the new crosshair and hitmarker system - v5_final

-Added custom CP icons - b1_rc1

-Added custom chat_english.txt file that makes several game messages 
more concise - b1_rc10

-Added custom player panels for the match status panel - b1_rc3

-Added custom targetID health value color customization line - b2_r1

-Added customization that disables the black background on the targetID - b1_rc7

-Added customized SourceScheme file, now the menu windows will match the overall theme - b1_rc6

-Added dropshadows to team names in all scoreboards - b1_rc11

-Added health value shadow color customization - b2_r1

-Added new mini Ubercharge bar customization - b1_rc4

-Added new, super minimal Payload and Payload Race progress bars - b1_rc6

-Added opaque killfeed background customization - b1_rc4

-Added override that moves the killstreak counter to the popular spot 
of over the killfeed, works with or without the kn edit mode. - b1_rc11

#####################################################################
#----CHANGED----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Adjusted Spy disguise status for better visibility of information as 
well as not overlapping with gravelpit C point icons - b1_rc6

-Adjusted TargetID elements for easier readability and better use of screen space - b1_rc6

-Changed CP icons to a flat color, in line with the new pastel shades - b1_rc9

-Changed CTF HUD to be more minimal, with new flag icons and more - b1_rc1

-Changed MvM sapper meter from the broesel meter style to the kn style (finally) - b1_rc9

-Changed Special Delivery HUD to be in line with the new CTF HUD - b1_rc1

-Changed most/all team colored panels to use new pastel shades of blue and red - b1_rc9

-Cleaned up MvM elements as a whole - b1_rc6, b2_r2, v5_final

-Cleaned up look of player health elements - b1_rc7
	└──Changed max health customization to read vertically and moved
	   it to sit just right of the main health value
	└──Moved status effect icons, resistance icons, and mannpower 
	   powerup icons to sit below the health value
	└──Switched default states of the health meters across the board 
	   to not having crosses, just text. Player health cross can be 
	   re-enabled with a customization file.

-Compressed and simplified the player destruction and robot destruction 
objective meters to no more than 40px tall to fit new height restrictions due 
to the timers being on the bottom. - b1_rc9

-Increased size of canel labels in the engy build/destroy menus - b3_rc2

-Made the code of several files make more sense - all, finished v5_final

-Moved all timers to the bottom of the screen above the objective meters, 
shrank them to not interfere with scoped view as sniper - b1_rc3
	└──Increased size of timer per request of a user - b1_rc5
	└──KOTH timers now look more like evehud in design, which KBN had
	   years ago - b1_rc5
	└──Round counter lights are above the KOTH timers and the CP icons - b1_rc5
	└──Shifted C objective of Gravelpit and Degroot Keep to above the
	   timer, janky but works. Plus, only three maps use this setup. - b1_rc5

-Moved comp/casual player panels to the bottom of the screen - b1_rc3
	└──Added override that puts them back at the top of the screen - b1_rc3
	└──Changed health bars for friendly team to be the full height of the 
	   panel - v5_final

-Moved HUD crosshairs to use Hypnotize's updated crosshair font, which has the
 best of the crosshair packs KBN was already using. - b3

-Moved vaccinator resistance icons next to the crosshair for Medic - b1_rc4

-Overhauled Disguise menu to a far more minimal style - b1_rc10

-Overhauled Engy build, destroy, and eureka effect menus into the hyperminimal 
style. Pip boy stuff is still there though. - b1_rc10

-Overhauled many customization systems: -b1_rc6, finished v5_final
	└──All customization options are now in the ^customizations
	   directory, including the ones below
	└──Color customizations are now in the "Colors" directory
	└──Crosshairs are simplified and now, guide images are in the
	   directory with the crosshairs file to help you choose the one you
	   want, all in the eponymous directory
	└──Hitmarkers now use a material file, which should save on some 
	   framerate for the game. Borrowed from Hypnotize; the file to
	   edit these as well as a guide is in the eponymous directory
	└──The old hitmarker/aim guide is now off by default, and can be
	   enabled with the file in the "Aim Guide" directory, though this
	   can also be accomplished with the included KonrWings crosshairs
	└──Unified the directory naming scheme. # directories are actively 
	   read by the game, _ directories are for bulk overrides, those 
	   being knedit mode and streamer mode. Updated the basefiles 
	   directory to be unique against those two other types.
	└──Updated directory names to better describe what the contained 
	   overrides actually do - b1_rc11

-Overhauled taunt menu alongside the build, destroy, and disguise menus. - b1_rc10

-Reduced opacity of engy and spy building panels and meters - b3_rc2

-Reduced opacity of metal meter and moved it closer to the crosshair, 
added custom color customization to it - b2_r3

-Reduced size of disguise status team color BG - b2_r3

-Reduced height of both the regular and arena winpanels - v5_final

-Removed the animated doors from the beginning and ending of matches - b1_rc3

-Set all Halloween minigames to consistent style - b1_rc9

-Set closed captions to disabled by default - b3_rc2

-Set TargetID to not have a background - v5_final
	└──Added customization for full BG and BG for the health only - v5_final

-Shrank some parts of the building panels, as well as added color customization to them - b2_r3

-Simplified the team selection menu - b1_rc9

-Updated Arena mode player counters for you deathrun nerds - b1_rc4

-Updated chat to use larger font and have a generally more modern look - b1_rc9

-Updated match summary screen to be more consistent - b1_rc2

-Updated readme files for both the GitHub and GB mirrors to be more 
in line with each other, and with informtation that has changed since 
they were last edited. - b1_rc5, finished v5_final

#####################################################################
#-----FIXED-----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Fixed added time popup to not overlap with the main timer value - b2_r1

-Fixed custom health base colors in the animations files - b2_r1

-Fixed game crashing when changing classes with the closed captions
disabled - b3_rc2

-Fixed issues with symbol and low weight fonts between Linux and Windows; 
KBN is authored in Linux and as such, I had it configured for Linux's 
janky font system. I have added flags for the game to use different files 
between both versions and separate size and weight for certain fonts. - b2_r2 (linux), b2_r3 (OSX)

-Fixed map voting panel on the end of round screen - b1_rc2

-Fixed numerous small tournament/pro league and comp MM issues - b1_rc3

-Fixed overlapping money and canteen elements - b1_rc9

-Fixed overlapping of charge meters for the Loose Cannon and demo shield charges - b1_rc1

-Fixed overtime line overlapping certain round timers. - b2_r2

-Fixed uncountable general font errors caused by me being lazy about adding 
fonts to clientscheme for previous updates. Also fixed a bunch of font 
weights and scoreboard fonts. -b1_rc1, b1_rc10

#####################################################################
#----REMOVED----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Removed old, now unused HUD crosshair fonts - b3_rc1

-Removed some unnecessary main menu buttons - b1_rc1

-Removed spy disguise outline animation - b2_r3

#####################################################################
#-----KNOWN BUGS-----################################################
#####################################################################

-Post-mortem freezeframe not showing data properly on first death
after joining game/server, works on second death

#####################################################################
#-----NOTES-----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-In my mind, the stuff you see in game is the HUD, and the menus are 
the UI (User Interface). As one, they form the UX (User Experience).
KBNHud has finally gone from a custom HUD with some menus to being a 
proper, complete UX replacement for TF2. The in game HUD, and (mostly) 
all menus are now custom.

#####################################################################
#-SPECIAL THANKS-####################################################
#####################################################################

-HUDS.TF Discord for all the help and advice

-Thanks to Sunflower, DeiStro, Verarch, and my other rc testers

-Hypnotize for the new materials and font file I have made heavy use 
of and retooled in the new UI system
