####################################################################################
#-----KBNHUD v503 - Langsam—Ruhevoll—Empfunden Edition - CHANGELOG-----#############
####################################################################################

###################################################################################
# Happy 10th birthday, KBNHud! How far things have come for both this HUD and for #
#  me. 27 updates since the 5th aniverssary update, v424. My first code project,  #
# started by a depressed 14 year old who still thought a decade was forever, and  #
#   had low hopes for seeing that "distant" future. TF2 was 4, and it is now 14.  #
#   I started this on a crappy iMac half a year before I scrounged the cash to    #
#   build a custom PC. Now I have a life, day job, a car of my own, and a plan.   #
#  Most of all, the success I saw with this HUD was the first step out of the pit #
#    I was in, and today I can say that I can genuinely smile at the end of the   #
# week, and when I help someone who has messaged me in my Discord server for help.#
# I could do this, this maddening and tedious thing, and maybe I could get out of #
# where I was. Thank you, all of you. Everyone who used and still uses this HUD,  #
#  or picked it up from huds.tf. It's been one hell of a ride, and I'm not going  #
#     anywhere. I owe this project too much to abandon it. When I think of an     #
#  improvement, I will add it. If VALVe decides to really update the game again,  #
#     I will be there with a patch. If a bug shows, I will do my best to help.    #
#  While you're here, give a listen to the song this update is named for, or as I #
# should say, movement. Symphony No. 3, Movement 6. (Gustav Mahler) It gets loud. #
#--Here's to the decades gone past and the decades to come. Take care, everyone!--#
###################################################################################

#####################################################################
#-----ADDED-----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Added more unique icons to the main menu, as too many had a similar
look of three horizontal lines.

-Added link buttons on the main menu that open the following in your
default browser: KBNHud's GitHub repo, KBNHud's HUDS.TF site, and my
own Discord server.

-Added color customization for the dropshadows of the ammo counters

-Added voice chat toggle to the main menu (this is a little iffy. It
shuts off voice just fine but re-enabling it is a bit wonky)

-Added transparent viewmodels customization at long last. Will work
if you have the proper mods installed to enable it.

-Added a button to the main menu that automatically launches a local
server running tr_walkway_rc2 if the user has the map installed/downloaded

-Added more abbreviations to chat_english.txt

#####################################################################
#----CHANGED----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Added two commented lines to the hitmarkers animations file
(/custom/kbnhud/scripts/animations/hitmarkers.txt), which when
uncommented, cause the HUD crosshairs to blink as hitmarkers in place
of separate ones. (For Malik794)

-Updated class selection to display class limits as a fractional; eg.
before it would say 2(3), now it will say 2/3. X meant either full or
that that class was not allowed; full will say 3/3, and if the class 
is banned, it will say 'Banned'. (Thanks Uncletopia)

-Changed queue popup to have expanded exit/manage button at the bottom
of the popup, this is to prevent interference with the KBNHud button.

-Overhauled the customizations (again) in order to make the HUD 
compatible with the TF2 HUD Editor, the spiritual successor to the
failed multi-installer from over half a decade ago. This requires a
simplified customizations folder. To combat any confusion, I finally
made a complete Wiki on the GitHub repo page, and an .html file in
^customizations links to this index with screenshots and instructions
for those not using the Editor. (#IF CONFUSED, CLICK THIS#.html)

-As part of the above, I changed the 4x3 fixes to an uncommentable.
in the ^customizations/#resolutions folder, 16x9 is uncommented, and
_4x3 is commented. By changing them to _16x9 and 4x3, the menus will
be changed to fit on non-widescreen aspect ratios.

-Disabled the team colored bar under player health by default instead
of it being enabled by default. The customization that hid it before
now activates it: player_health_teamcolor_hudplayerhealth.res

-Made the damage indicators that show where you were hit from less
obtrusive (Thanks Horse)

-Changed the default HUD crosshair color to bright green (0 255 0 255)

-Changed default damage numbers/metal spent color to fuschia (255 0 255 255)

-Changed low health and low ammo blink #2 colors to be more different
from the initial #1 blink colors, this makes being at low health or
low on ammo much more obvious and eye-catching

-Changed destroy menu to no longer use icons, merely say
"Destroy (building)" in red text, this allowed me to bring the vertical
height of the destroy menu down to match the footprint of the build
menu, because I'm obsessive like that.

-Changed build menu to use the same metal color as the main indicator
when able to build a building. It still displays red when you're short
on metal.

-Updated Player Destruction elements to fit the general styling of
objective displays

-Reverted back to older, non-centered TargetID due to numerous unfixable
issues with centered TargetID. This also allows health to be displayed
in disguise status, and for floating health to function. Rejoice, MvM players.
Added a dropshadow to the text displaying the name of who/what you
are looking at to improve general visibility versus the version found in v5.

Changed Fighter Pilot Crosshairs to a single, universal file that
works no matter what aspect ratio and resolution you are using.
(about damn time) This was done to simplify and un-cramp the KBNHud
page in the HUD Editor. It also allows for simplifying the associated
Wiki page for the HUD and greater ease of use for less experienced users.

#####################################################################
#-----FIXED-----#####################################################
#####################################################################

-Fixed remaining issues with the symbol fonts used for the menus in
Linux. Also renamed the symbol font file to match kbn as it is 
"custom" enough for me to be good with calling it my own.

-Fixed inconsistencies with kerning of the HUD crosshairs in Linux.
I feel this is prudent given the coming advent of the Steam Deck.
Some were working out of the box, but very few. Most were very much
out of alignment as compared to when the HUD is run in Windows, and
impossible to align with xpos and ypos. Pushed these changes to
the core version of Hypnotize's crosshairs pack on GitHub for all to 
use.

-Fixed inconsistencies with Demoman charge meters

-Fixed main menu background being blurry at low settings

-Fixed MvM Upgrades summary not showing for selected item

-Fixed the popup for healing and damage not moving with KNEdit mode

-Fixed several halloween things

#####################################################################
#----REMOVED----#####################################################
#####################################################################



#####################################################################
#-----KNOWN BUGS-----################################################
#####################################################################

:^)

#####################################################################
#-----NOTES-----#####################################################
#####################################################################



#####################################################################
#-SPECIAL THANKS-####################################################
#####################################################################

-A big thanks to everyone else not mentioned here who lent a hand or 
maybe some code over these 10 long years, whether you're still around 
in this or not. It's been an honor and a pleasure, and I wish all of 
you the best on your continuing paths; while I walk mine. 
Let's see if TF2 lives for another 10 years.
